<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Charalampos A. Lazaris on Charalampos A. Lazaris</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Charalampos A. Lazaris on Charalampos A. Lazaris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Charalampos A. Lazaris &amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dynamic 3D Chromatin Architecture Landscape of Acute Leukemia</title>
      <link>/talk/the-dynamic-3d-chromatin-architecture-landscape-of-acute-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 19:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/the-dynamic-3d-chromatin-architecture-landscape-of-acute-leukemia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Aristotelis Tsirigos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: Andreas Kloetgen, Palaniraja Thandapani, Panagiotis Ntziachristos, Charalampos Lazaris, Xufeng Chen, Hai Hu, Sofia Bakogianni, Jingjing Wang, Thomas Trimarchi, Yixing Zhu, Iannis Aifantis&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Nuclear Organization</title>
      <link>/project/3d-nuclear-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 18:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/3d-nuclear-organization/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOTCH1 Hijacks the Stress Response Machinery in T Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia</title>
      <link>/post/notch1-hijacks-the-stress-response-machinery-in-t-acute-lymphoblastic-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 17:53:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/notch1-hijacks-the-stress-response-machinery-in-t-acute-lymphoblastic-leukemia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our study on how NOTCH1 directly regulates the expression of HSF1 and other key heat-shock proteins in T-ALL, supporting the survival of cancer cells, is now available online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Oncogenic NOTCH1 controls transcriptional activation of the heat shock response in T cell acute lymphoblastic &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hashtag/leukemia?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;#leukemia&lt;/a&gt; and uncovers potential biomarkers of sensitivity to HSP90 inhibition: &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/U9mxcLTWm6&#34;&gt;https://t.co/U9mxcLTWm6&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/2brz23jTKG&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/2brz23jTKG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Nature Medicine (@NatureMedicine) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/NatureMedicine/status/1022481370923364353?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;July 26, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oncogenic Hijacking of the Stress Response Machinery in T Cell Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia</title>
      <link>/publication/oncogenic-hijacking-of-the-stress-response-machinery-in-t-cell-acute-lymphoblastic-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 12:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/oncogenic-hijacking-of-the-stress-response-machinery-in-t-cell-acute-lymphoblastic-leukemia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy-of-this-website&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy of this website&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charalampos Lazaris  operates the &lt;a href=&#34;https://chlazaris.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Charalampos A. Lazaris&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt; website, which provides the SERVICE.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service, the Charalampos A. Lazaris website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at &lt;a href=&#34;https://chlazaris.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://chlazaris.github.io&lt;/a&gt;, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-collection-and-use&#34;&gt;Information Collection and Use&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;log-data&#34;&gt;Log Data&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (&amp;ldquo;IP&amp;rdquo;) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cookies&#34;&gt;Cookies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our website uses these &amp;ldquo;cookies&amp;rdquo; to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;service-providers&#34;&gt;Service Providers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To facilitate our Service;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide the Service on our behalf;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To perform Service-related services; or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;links-to-other-sites&#34;&gt;Links to Other Sites&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;children-s-privacy&#34;&gt;Children’s Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-this-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Changes to This Privacy Policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page. This privacy policy was created with the GDPR Generator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic 3D chromosomal landscapes in acute leukemia</title>
      <link>/talk/dynamic-3d-chromosomal-landscapes-in-acute-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/dynamic-3d-chromosomal-landscapes-in-acute-leukemia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Palaniraja Thandapani&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: Andreas Kloetgen, Charalampos Lazaris, Xufeng Chen, Panagiotis Ntziachristos, Aristotelis Tsirigos and Iannis Aifantis&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic 3D Chromosomal Landscapes in T-ALL</title>
      <link>/talk/dynamic-3d-chromosomal-landscapes-in-t-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 14:28:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/dynamic-3d-chromosomal-landscapes-in-t-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Andreas Kloetgen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: Palaniraja Thandapani, Charalampos Lazaris, Panagiotis Ntziachristos, Aristotelis Tsirigos and Iannis Aifantis&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role of Dysregulated Cytokine Signaling and Bacterial Triggers in the Pathogenesis of Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma</title>
      <link>/publication/role-of-dysregulated-cytokine-signaling-and-bacterial-triggers-in-the-pathogenesis-of-cutaneous-t-cell-lymphoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 15:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/role-of-dysregulated-cytokine-signaling-and-bacterial-triggers-in-the-pathogenesis-of-cutaneous-t-cell-lymphoma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stratification of TAD Boundaries Reveals Preferential Insulation of Super Enhancers by Strong Boundaries</title>
      <link>/publication/stratification-of-tad-boundaries-reveals-preferential-insulation-of-super-enhancers-by-strong-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 22:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/stratification-of-tad-boundaries-reveals-preferential-insulation-of-super-enhancers-by-strong-boundaries/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Grade Astrocytoma Mutations in IDH1, P53, and ATRX Cooperate to Block Differentiation of Human Neural Stem Cells via Repression of SOX2</title>
      <link>/publication/low-grade-astrocytoma-mutations-in-idh1-p53-and-atrx-cooperate-to-block-differentiation-of-human-neural-stem-cells-via-repression-of-sox2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 16:11:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/low-grade-astrocytoma-mutations-in-idh1-p53-and-atrx-cooperate-to-block-differentiation-of-human-neural-stem-cells-via-repression-of-sox2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pleiotropic Genetic Effects on Cell Morphology Are Mediated by Underlying Relationships Among Single Cell Morphological Features</title>
      <link>/talk/pleiotropic-genetic-effects-on-cell-morphology-are-mediated-by-underlying-relationships-among-single-cell-morphological-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 15:07:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/pleiotropic-genetic-effects-on-cell-morphology-are-mediated-by-underlying-relationships-among-single-cell-morphological-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Kerry Geiler-Samerotte&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: Austin Taylor, Harris (Charalampos) Lazaris, Chelsea Ramjeawan, Naomi Ziv, Mark Siegal&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chromatin Organization Alterations in Critical Oncogenic Loci in Leukemia</title>
      <link>/talk/chromatin-organization-alterations-in-critical-oncogenic-loci-in-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 15:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/chromatin-organization-alterations-in-critical-oncogenic-loci-in-leukemia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Aristotelis Tsirigos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Charalampos Lazaris&lt;/em&gt;, Panagiotis Ntziachristos, Nikolaos Kourtis, Stephen Kelly and Iannis Aifantis&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De novo PATRR-mediated t(3;8) balanced translocation associated with clear cell renal cell carcinoma</title>
      <link>/talk/de-novo-patrr-mediated-balanced-translocation-associated-with-clear-cell-renal-cell-carcinoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 15:43:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/de-novo-patrr-mediated-balanced-translocation-associated-with-clear-cell-renal-cell-carcinoma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presenter&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Marilena Melas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Other authors&lt;/em&gt;: Kevin J. McDonnell, Chris K. Edlund, Sarah J.Tash, Duveen Y. Sturgeon, Charalampos Lazaris, Chenxu Qu, Peter J. Gruber, Thomas W. Glover, Beverly S. Emanuel, Stephen B.Gruber&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opposing Functions of H2BK120 Ubiquitylation and H3K79 Methylation in the Regulation of Pluripotency by the Paf1 Complex</title>
      <link>/publication/opposing-functions-of-h2bk120-ubiquitylation-and-h3k79-methylation-in-the-regulation-of-pluripotency-by-the-paf1-complex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 17:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/opposing-functions-of-h2bk120-ubiquitylation-and-h3k79-methylation-in-the-regulation-of-pluripotency-by-the-paf1-complex/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HiC-bench: comprehensive and reproducible Hi-C data analysis designed for parameter exploration and benchmarking</title>
      <link>/publication/hic-bench-comprehensive-and-reproducible-hi-c-data-analysis-designed-for-parameter-exploration-and-benchmarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 17:25:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/hic-bench-comprehensive-and-reproducible-hi-c-data-analysis-designed-for-parameter-exploration-and-benchmarking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
